let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the given is the SI Unit of Electric Current?",
    answer: "Ampere",
    options: [
      "Ohm",
      "Ampere",
      "Volt",
      "Faraday"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A fuse wire is inserted in which wire?",
    answer: "Live wire ",
    options: [
      "Live wire ",
      "In the neutral wire ",
      "In the earth wire",
      "May be connected in any line"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The rate of flow of an electric charge is known as :",
    answer: "Electric current",
    options: [
      "Electric Potential",
      "Electric conductance",
      "Electric current",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The amount of work done in joules, when one unit electric charge moves from one point to another point in an electric circuit is called :",
    answer: "Potential Difference",
    options: [
      "Electric Current",
      "Electric Resistance",
      "Electric Conductance",
      "Potential Difference"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The relation between potential difference (V) and current (I) is",
    answer: "V2 α I2 ",
    options: [
      " V α I2",
      "V α 1/I",
      "V2 α I",
      "V2 α I2 "
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The relation between potential difference (V) and current (I) was discovered by :",
    answer: "Ohm",
    options: [
      " Newton",
      "Ampere",
      "Ohm",
      " Volta"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "On which of the given resistance does not depend :",
    answer: " Density",
    options: [
      " Length of conductor",
      " Area of cross-section",
      "Temperature",
      " Density"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In parallel combination of electrical appliances, total electrical power",
    answer: "Remain same",
    options: [
      " Increase",
      " Decrease",
      " Does not change",
      "Remain same"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How the charge will flow?",
    answer: "By applying potential difference",
    options: [
      " By heating them",
      "By applying potential difference",
      " Both",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In SI unit, JC⁻¹ is equal to",
    answer: " Newton's law",
    options: [
      " Newton's law",
      "  Volt",
      " Pascal",
      "Omega"
    ]
  },
  
];